Undergraduate Alumni Records, 18th Century 1748-1799: Preliminary Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Series 1: Alumni Files, 1748-1799; 1382 files
  - Ramsay, Nathaniel, 1767; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 17)
  - Schenck, William, 1767; portion of 1 box (Box 17)
  - Stockton, Samuel Witham, 1767; portion of 1 box (Box 17)
  - Stoddard, Josiah, 1767; portion of 1 box (Box 17)
  - Vance, Hugh, 1767; portion of 1 box (Box 17)
  - Blackwell, Robert, 1768; portion of 1 box (Box 17)
  - Brevard, Ephraim, 1768; portion of 1 box (Box 17)
  - Culbertson, Samuel, 1768; portion of 1 box (Box 17)
  - Edwards, Pierpont, 1768; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 17)
  - Houston, William Churchill, 1768; portion of 1 box (Box 17)
  - Knowles, Isaac, 1768; portion of 1 box (Box 17)
  - Osborne, Adlai, 1768; portion of 1 box (Box 18)
  - Parker, Samuel, 1768; portion of 1 box (Box 18)
  - Reese, Thomas, 1768; portion of 1 box (Box 18)
  - Sebring, Michael, 1768; portion of 1 box (Box 18)
  - Smith, Thomas, 1768; portion of 1 box (Box 18)
  - Story, Isaac, 1768; portion of 1 box (Box 18)
  - Van Bunschooten, Elias, 1768; portion of 1 box (Box 18)
  - West, Benjamin, 1768; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 18)
  - Beatty, John, 1769; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 18)
  - Blair, William Lawrence, 1769; portion of 1 box (Box 18)
  - Brevard, Joel, 1769; portion of 1 box (Box 18)
  - Burnet, Matthias, Jr., 1769; portion of 1 box (Box 18)
  - Channing, William, 1769; portion of 1 box (Box 18)
  - Cooper, Caleb, 1769; portion of 1 box (Box 18)
  - Davenport, John, 1769; portion of 1 box (Box 18)
  - Davies, John Rogers, 1769; portion of 1 box (Box 18)
  - DeWitt, Peter (Petrus), 1769; portion of 1 box (Box 18)
  - Dickinson, John, 1769; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Henry, John, III, 1769; portion of 1 box (Box 18)
  - Linn, James, 1769; portion of 1 box (Box 19)
  - McDougall, John Alexander, 1769; portion of 1 box (Box 19)
  - Melvill (Melville), Thomas, 1769; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 19)
  - Niles, Samuel, III, 1769; portion of 1 box (Box 19)
  - Reed, Jesse, 1769; portion of 1 box (Box 19)
  - Smith, Samuel Stanhope, 1769; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 19)
  - Stockton, Philip, 1769; portion of 1 box (Box 19)
  - Thayer, Elihu, 1769; portion of 1 box (Box 19)
  - Willcocks, William, Jr., 1769; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 19)
  - Zubly, David, 1769; portion of 1 box (Box 19)
  - Baldwin, Cornelius, 1770; portion of 1 box (Box 19)
  - Baldwin, Samuel, 1770; portion of 1 box (Box 19)
  - Blydenburg, John, 1770; portion of 1 box (Box 19)
  - Bowden, John, 1770; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 19)
  - Campbell, John, 1770; portion of 1 box (Box 20)
  - Frelinghuysen, Frederick, 1770; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 20)
  - Hartt, Joshua, 1770; portion of 1 box (Box 20)
  - Horton, Azariah, Jr., 1770; portion of 1 box (Box 20)
  - Irwin, Nathaniel, 1770; portion of 1 box (Box 20)
  - McPherrin, Thomas, 1770; portion of 1 box (Box 20)
  - Ogden, John Cosens, 1770; portion of 1 box (Box 20)
  - Perkins, Nathan, 1770; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 20)
  - Pomeroy, Josiah, 1770; portion of 1 box (Box 20)
  - Russell, Caleb, 1770; portion of 1 box (Box 20)
  - Smith, George, 1770; portion of 1 box (Box 20)
  - Smith, Isaac, 1770; portion of 1 box (Box 20)
  - Smith, John, 1770; portion of 1 box (Box 20)
  - Stewart, Robert, 1770; portion of 1 box (Box 21)
  - Taylor, John, 1770; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 21)
  - Tracy, Stephen, 1770; portion of 1 box (Box 21)
  - Wallace, Caleb, 1770; portion of 1 box (Box 21)
  - Wallace, Caleb, 1770; portion of 1 box (Box 21)
  - Williams, Bedford, 1770; portion of 1 box (Box 21)
  - Williamson, Matthias, 1770; portion of 1 box (Box 21)
  - Wilson, James, 1770; portion of 1 box (Box 21)
  - Witherspoon, James, 1770; portion of 1 box (Box 21)
  - Bedford, Gunning, Jr., 1771; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 21)
  - Black, John, 1771; portion of 1 box (Box 21)
  - Brackenridge, Hugh Henry, 1771; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 21)
  - Campbell, Donald, 1771; portion of 1 box (Box 22)
  - Cheesman, Edmund, 1771; portion of 1 box (Box 22)
  - Freneau, Philip Morin (file 1), 1771; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 22)
  - Freneau, Philip Morin (file 2), 1771; portion of 1 box (Box 22)
  - Madison, James, Jr., 1771; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 22)
  - McKnight, Charles, 1771; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 22)
  - Ross, Joseph, 1771; portion of 1 box (Box 23)
  - Scott, William, 1771; portion of 1 box (Box 23)
  - Spring, Samuel, 1771; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 23)
  - Taylor, James, 1771; portion of 1 box (Box 23)
  - Williamson, Jacob, 1771; portion of 1 box (Box 23)
  - Williamson, James, 1771; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Alexander, Isaac, 1772; portion of 1 box (Box 23)
  - Allen, Moses, 1772; portion of 1 box (Box 23)
  - Archibald, Robert, 1772; portion of 1 box (Box 23)
  - Bradford, William, Jr., 1772; portion of 1 box (Box 23)
  - Bryan, Andrew, 1772; portion of 1 box (Box 23)
  - Burr, Aaron, Jr. (file one), 1772; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 23)
  - Burr, Aaron, Jr. (file two), 1772; portion of 1 box (Box 23)
  - DeBow, John, 1772; portion of 1 box (Box 23)
  - Eckley, Joseph, 1772; portion of 1 box (Box 23)
  - Evans, Israel, 1772; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 24)
  - Findley, Ebenezer, 1772; portion of 1 box (Box 24)
  - Fithian, Philip Vickers, 1772; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 24)
  - Grier, James, 1772; portion of 1 box (Box 24)
  - Grier, James, 1772; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Hodge, Andrew, 1772; portion of 1 box (Box 24)
  - Hodge, Andrew, 1772; portion of 1 box (Box 24)
  - Hoge, Andre, 1772; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Hunter, Andrew II, 1772; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 24)
  - Hustop, David, 1772; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Keith, Robert, 1772; portion of 1 box (Box 24)
  - Linn, William, 1772; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 24)
  - Livingston, William Smith, 1772; portion of 1 box (Box 24)
  - Luckey, George, 1772; portion of 1 box (Box 24)
  - McClean, Archibald, 1772; portion of 1 box (Box 24)
  - McCorkle, Samuel Eusebius, 1772; portion of 1 box (Box 24)
  - McMillan, John, 1772; portion of 1 box (Box 25)
  - Reese, Oliver, 1772; portion of 1 box (Box 25)
  - Templeton, James, 1772; portion of 1 box (Box 25)
  - Woodruff, Hunloke, 1772; portion of 1 box (Box 25)
  - Armstrong, James Francis, 1773; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 25)
  - Bard, David, 1773; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 25)
  - Beekman, William, 1773; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 25)
  - Bradford, Ebenezer, 1773; portion of 1 box (Box 25)
  - Cooke, Stephen, 1773; portion of 1 box (Box 25)
  - Craig, Archibald, 1773; portion of 1 box (Box 25)
  - Craig, Hugh, 1773; portion of 1 box (Box 25)
  - Davenport, Franklin, 1773; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 25)
  - Dod, Thaddeus, 1773; portion of 1 box (Box 25)
  - Duffield, John, 1773; portion of 1 box (Box 25)
  - Dunlap, James, 1773; portion of 1 box (Box 25)
  - Graham, William, 1773; portion of 1 box (Box 26)
  - Hasbrouck, James (Jacobus), 1773; portion of 1 box (Box 26)
  - Hodge, Hugh, 1773; portion of 1 box (Box 26)
  - Imlay, William Eugene, 1773; portion of 1 box (Box 26)
  - King, Andrew, 1773; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 26)
  - Lee, Henry, Jr. (file one), 1773; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 26)
  - Lee, Henry, Jr. (file two), 1773; portion of 1 box (Box 26)
  - Lewis, Morgan, 1773; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 26)
  - Linn, John, 1773; portion of 1 box (Box 26)
  - McConnell, James, 1773; portion of 1 box (Box 26)
  - McCulloch, James, 1773; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 26)
  - McKnight, John, 1773; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 27)
  - Ogden, Aaron, 1773; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 27)
  - Platt, Richard, 1773; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 27)
  - Smith, Belcher Peartree, 1773; portion of 1 box (Box 27)
  - Smith, John Blair, 1773; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 27)
  - Smith, William Richard, 1773; portion of 1 box (Box 27)
  - Tate, James, 1773; portion of 1 box (Box 27)
  - Waugh, Samuel, 1773; portion of 1 box (Box 27)
  - Wilson, Lewis Feuilleteau, 1773; portion of 1 box (Box 27)
  - Witherspoon, John, Jr., 1773; portion of 1 box (Box 27)
  - Balch, Stephen Bloomer, 1774; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 27)
  - Beekman, Abraham Keteltas, 1774; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 27)
  - Bradford, William, 1774; portion of 1 box (Box 27)
  - Breck, Daniel, 1774; portion of 1 box (Box 27)
  - Colhoun, John Ewing, 1774; portion of 1 box (Box 28)
  - Cumming, John Noble, 1774; portion of 1 box (Box 28)
  - Fish, Peter, 1774; portion of 1 box (Box 28)
  - Forman, Jonathan, 1774; portion of 1 box (Box 28)
  - Fret, Flounce, 1774; portion of 1 box (Box 28)
  - Gale, George, 1774; portion of 1 box (Box 28)
  - Glover, John, 1774; portion of 1 box (Box 28)
  - Hall, James, 1774; portion of 1 box (Box 28)
  - Hazard, Joseph, 1774; portion of 1 box (Box 28)
  - Hodge, Hugh, Jr., 1774; portion of 1 box (Box 28)
  - Jennifer, Thomas, 1774; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Jordan, John, 1774; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Leake, Samuel, 1774; portion of 1 box (Box 28)
  - Livingston, Henry Brockholst, 1774; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 28)
  - Mason, Jonathan, Jr., 1774; portion of 1 box (Box 29)
  - McCaule, Thomas Harris, 1774; portion of 1 box (Box 28)
  - Morris, Lewis IV, 1774; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 29)
  - Peck, John, 1774; portion of 1 box (Box 29)
  - Peterson, William, 1774; portion of 1 box (Box 29)
  - Phillips, John, 1774; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Phillips, John Lott, 1774; portion of 1 box Contains oversize material. (Box 29)
  - Smith, William Stephens, 1774; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 29)
  - Tate, James, 1774; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Troup, Robert, 1774; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Van Cortlandt, Nicholas Bayard, 1774; portion of 1 box (Box 29)
  - Warford, John, 1774; portion of 1 box (Box 29)
  - Whitwell, Samuel, 1774; portion of 1 box (Box 29)
  - Witherspoon, David, 1774; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 29)
  - Armstrong, John, 1775; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 30)
  - Beatty, Charles Clinton, 1775; portion of 1 box (Box 30)
  - Blair, John Durbarrow, 1775; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 30)
  - Bostwick, William, 1775; portion of 1 box (Box 30)
  - Brown, James, 1775; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Bruyn, Jacobus Severyn, 1775; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 30)
  - Burnet, Ichabod, 1775; portion of 1 box (Box 30)
  - Claypoole, William, 1775; portion of 1 box (Box 30)
  - Craighead, Thomas, 1775; portion of 1 box (Box 30)
  - Crawford, Edward, 1775; portion of 1 box (Box 30)
  - Doak, Samuel, 1775; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 30)
  - Duncan, James, 1775; portion of 1 box (Box 30)
  - Ely, Joseph, 1775; portion of 1 box (Box 30)
  - Elzey, Arnold, 1775; portion of 1 box (Box 30)
  - Evans, John, 1775; portion of 1 box (Box 30)
  - Finley, Joseph Lewis, 1775; portion of 1 box (Box 30)
  - Fish, Nicholas, 1775; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 31)
  - Forman, Jonathan, 1775; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Henry, William Blair, 1775; portion of 1 box (Box 31)
  - Jenifer, Daniel of St. Thomas, 1775; portion of 1 box (Box 31)
  - Joline, John, 1775; portion of 1 box (Box 31)
  - Keith, Isaac Stockton, 1775; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 31)
  - Kirkpatrick, Andrew, 1775; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 31)
  - Lee, Charles, 1775; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 31)
  - Lewis, George, 1775; portion of 1 box (Box 31)
  - Livingston, William Alexander, 1775; portion of 1 box (Box 31)
  - Ludlow, John, 1775; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Macay, Spruce, 1775; portion of 1 box (Box 31)
  - Malen, James, 1775; portion of 1 box (Box 31)
  - Martin, Daniel, 1775; portion of 1 box (Box 31)
  - McRee, James, 1775; portion of 1 box (Box 31)
  - Montgomery, John, 1775; portion of 1 box (Box 31)
  - Neal, Thomas, 1775; portion of 1 box (Box 31)
  - Neal, Thomas, 1775; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Pigeon, John, Jr., 1775; portion of 1 box (Box 32)
  - Reid, James R., 1775; portion of 1 box (Box 32)
  - Rodgers, John Richardson Bayard, 1775; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 32)
  - Scott, Archibald, 1775; portion of 1 box (Box 32)
  - Scudder, John Anderson, 1775; portion of 1 box (Box 32)
  - Springer, John, 1775; portion of 1 box (Box 32)
  - Sprott, Thomas, 1775; portion of 1 box (Box 32)
  - Ten Broeck, Jacob, 1775; portion of 1 box (Box 32)
  - Ten Broeck, Jacob, 1775; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Tichenor, Isaac, 1775; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 32)
  - Trezevant, John Timothy, 1775; portion of 1 box (Box 32)
  - Van Dyke, John, 1775; portion of 1 box (Box 32)
  - Wilkinson, John, 1775; portion of 1 box (Box 32)
  - Alexander, Nathaniel, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 32)
  - Armstrong, John, Jr., 1776; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 32)
  - Beekman, James, Jr., 1776; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 32)
  - Bishop, Benjamin, 1776; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Brown, John, 1776; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Calvin, Bartholomew Scott, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 33)
  - Clark, Gardner, 1776; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Clark, Lardner, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 33)
  - Coates, William, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 33)
  - Coats, William, 1776; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Davie, William Richardson, 1776; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 33)
  - Dayton, Jonathan, 1776; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 33)
  - Dean, Nicholas, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 33)
  - Erwin, Benjamin, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 33)
  - Faitoute, George, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 33)
  - Finley, John Evans, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 33)
  - Freneau, Peter, 1776; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Haslop, David, 1776; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Henderson, Joseph Washington, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 33)
  - Henry, Robert Jenkins, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 33)
  - Henry, Robert Rosbrough, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 33)
  - Hyslop, David, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 33)
  - Johnes, William, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 33)
  - Johnston, Andrew, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 33)
  - Jordan, John, 1776; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - King, Samuel, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 33)
  - Kittera, John Wilkes, 1776; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 34)
  - Lane, Joseph Flavius, 1776; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 34)
  - Leake, John, 1776; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 34)
  - Lewis, Charles, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 34)
  - Livingston, Henry Philip, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 34)
  - Martin, Robert, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 34)
  - McAllister, John, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 34)
  - McCallister, John, 1776; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - McCandless, Moses, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 34)
  - McConkey, Samuel, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 34)
  - McCrea, Robert, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 34)
  - McGee, Samuel, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 34)
  - Montgomery, William, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 34)
  - Mount, Richard, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 34)
  - Neil, Elisha, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 34)
  - Olden, Benjamin, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 34)
  - Parker, Thomas, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 34)
  - Perkins, Eliphaz, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 35)
  - Pierson, Cyrus, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 35)
  - Pintard, John, 1776; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 35)
  - Ramsay, James, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 35)
  - Ramsay, William, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 35)
  - Read, Archibald Campbell, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 35)
  - Rhea, Aaron, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 35)
  - Rue, Joseph, 1776; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 35)
  - Rutherford, John, 1776; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 35)
  - Semple, Nathaniel Welshard, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 35)
  - Shannon, Samuel, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 35)
  - Snowden, Benjamin Parker, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 35)
  - Stockton, Benjamin Brearley, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 35)
  - Vernon, William H., 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 35)
  - Wade, Nehemiah, Jr., 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 35)
  - Wilson, James Lewis, 1776; portion of 1 box (Box 35)
  - Bailey, Theodorus, 1777; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 36)
  - Bancker, Abraham, 1777; portion of 1 box (Box 36)
  - Barber, William, 1777; portion of 1 box (Box 36)
  - Bayard, James Ashton, 1777; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 36)
  - Bibb, Richard, 1777; portion of 1 box (Box 36)
  - Blewer, George, 1777; portion of 1 box (Box 36)
  - Brownfield, John, 1777; portion of 1 box (Box 36)
  - Conant, Jacob, 1777; portion of 1 box (Box 36)
  - Crawford, James, 1777; portion of 1 box (Box 36)
  - Fish, Nicholas, 1777; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 36)
  - Graham, Alexander, 1777; portion of 1 box (Box 36)
  - Graham, John, 1777; portion of 1 box (Box 36)
  - Hackett, Samuel Reading, 1777; portion of 1 box (Box 36)
  - Halsey, Luther, 1777; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 36)
  - Hanna, James, 1777; portion of 1 box (Box 36)
  - Hawkins, Benjamin, 1777; portion of 1 box (Box 36)
  - Hawkins, Joseph, 1777; portion of 1 box (Box 36)
  - Hazard, George W., 1777; portion of 1 box (Box 36)
  - Hoops, Adam, Jr., 1777; portion of 1 box (Box 36)
  - Hopkins, Levi, 1777; portion of 1 box (Box 36)
  - Jenifer, Daniel, 1777; portion of 1 box (Box 37)
  - Jordan, John, 1777; portion of 1 box (Box 37)
  - Longstreet, Richard, 1777; portion of 1 box (Box 37)
  - Lowther, Tristrim, 1777; portion of 1 box (Box 37)
  - McCalla, Thomas Harrison, 1777; portion of 1 box (Box 37)
  - Noel, John, 1777; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Noel, John Young, 1777; portion of 1 box (Box 37)
  - Perkins, Matthew, 1777; portion of 1 box (Box 37)
  - Scott, Lewis Allaire, 1777; portion of 1 box (Box 37)
  - Smith, Abraham, 1777; portion of 1 box (Box 37)
  - Tennent, Gilbert, Jr., 1777; portion of 1 box (Box 37)
  - Thane, Samuel, 1777; portion of 1 box (Box 37)
  - Trottman, John, 1777; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Van Rensselaer, S., 1777; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Vickers, Samuel, 1777; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 37)
  - White, John, 1777; portion of 1 box (Box 37)
  - Boyd, William, 1778; portion of 1 box (Box 37)
  - Brown, John, 1778; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 37)
  - Brown, John, 1778; portion of 1 box (Box 37)
  - Dunlap, Benjamin, 1778; portion of 1 box (Box 37)
  - Ellet (Ellit, Elett), John, 1778; portion of 1 box (Box 37)
  - Halkerston, William, 1778; portion of 1 box (Box 37)
  - Macon, Nathaniel, 1778; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 38)
  - McDonald, James, 1778; portion of 1 box (Box 38)
  - Morton, Jacob, 1778; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 38)
  - Neil, Elisha, 1778; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Pettit, Andrew, 1778; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 38)
  - Ross, William, 1778; portion of 1 box (Box 38)
  - Scott, Lewis, 1778; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Scudder, Joseph, 1778; portion of 1 box (Box 38)
  - Smith, Abraham, 1778; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Smith, Jesse (Jessy, Jesles), 1778; portion of 1 box (Box 38)
  - Smith, John, 1778; portion of 1 box (Box 38)
  - Smith, William, 1778; portion of 1 box (Box 38)
  - Stephens (Stevens), William, 1778; portion of 1 box (Box 38)
  - Thatcher (Thacher), Daniel, 1778; portion of 1 box (Box 38)
  - Trotman, John, 1778; portion of 1 box (Box 38)
  - Wharry (Wherry), Robert, 1778; portion of 1 box (Box 38)
  - Wilson, Peter, 1778; portion of 1 box (Box 38)
  - Woods, Matthew, 1778; portion of 1 box (Box 38)
  - Bayard, Andrew, 1779; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 38)
  - Lee, Richard Bland, 1779; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 38)
  - McAllister, Matthew, 1779; portion of 1 box (Box 39)
  - Merchant, George, 1779; portion of 1 box (Box 39)
  - Riddle, James, 1779; portion of 1 box (Box 39)
  - Stockton, Richard, 1779; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 39)
  - West, George, 1779; portion of 1 box (Box 39)
  - Woodruff, Aaron Dickinson, 1779; portion of 1 box (Box 39)
  - Brown, William, 1780; portion of 1 box (Box 39)
  - Coles, Samuel, 1780; portion of 1 box (Box 39)
  - Rhea, John, 1780; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 39)
  - Roosevelt, James, 1780; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 39)
  - Russell, Alexander, 1780; portion of 1 box (Box 39)
  - Stockton, Ebenezer, 1780; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 39)
  - Van Ingen, William, 1780; portion of 1 box (Box 39)
  - Venable, Abraham Bedford, 1780; portion of 1 box (Box 39)
  - Venable, Samuel Woodson, 1780; portion of 1 box (Box 39)
  - Watkins, William, 1780; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Wherry, Robert, 1780; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Whorry, Robert, 1780; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Clark, Joseph, 1781; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 40)
  - Crawford, William, 1781; portion of 1 box (Box 40)
  - Giles, William Branch, 1781; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 40)
  - James, Francis Jefferson, 1781; portion of 1 box Contains oversize material. (Box 40)
  - Livingston, Edward, 1781; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 40)
  - Smith, Robert, 1781; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 40)
  - VanTugen, William, 1781; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Ball, Spencer, 1782; portion of 1 box (Box 40)
  - Elmendorf, Lucas Conrad, 1782; portion of 1 box (Box 40)
  - Elmendorf, Peter Edmund, 1782; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 40)
  - Hanna, John Andre, 1782; portion of 1 box (Box 40)
  - Johnston, John, 1782; portion of 1 box (Box 40)
  - Kennedy, William, 1782; portion of 1 box (Box 40)
  - Mahon, William, 1782; portion of 1 box (Box 40)
  - Morton, John, 1782; portion of 1 box (Box 41)
  - Pearson, Robert, 1782; portion of 1 box (Box 41)
  - Ten Eyck, Richard (Dirck), 1782; portion of 1 box (Box 41)
  - Van Rensselaer, Stephen, 1782; portion of 1 box (Box 41)
  - Venable, Richard N., 1782; portion of 1 box (Box 41)
  - West, Daniel, 1782; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - West, George, 1782; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Wilson, Samuel, 1782; portion of 1 box (Box 41)
  - Beach, Samuel, 1783; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 41)
  - Clements, William, 1783; portion of 1 box (Box 41)
  - Drayton, John, 1783; portion of 1 box (Box 41)
  - Ford, Timothy, 1783; portion of 1 box (Box 41)
  - Green, Ashbel, 1783; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 41)
  - Holmes, Obadiah, 1783; portion of 1 box (Box 41)
  - Hunt, James (Green, Greene), 1783; portion of 1 box (Box 41)
  - Lawrence, Nathaniel, 1783; portion of 1 box (Box 41)
  - LeRoy, Jacob, 1783; portion of 1 box (Box 42)